{
    "id": "ca9d5ae894814a12bb59fcc3a9717298",
    "title": "Grammar Exercise (Intermediate Level)",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "When I saw him he ………………. bed-ridden for two months.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "has been",
                "had been"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ca7677663c0b46989db7e01170cfb511"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………… college last year.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "left",
                "have left",
                "had left",
                "was leaving"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7f20f6544a924ebeba80adbcd5baa12c"
        },
        {
            "question": "There ....................... a famine in Bengal in",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "has been",
                "had been"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f663c2cac76c4ceb9a28d9c4fa1bb193"
        },
        {
            "question": "The child ………………. to drink the milk.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "made",
                "was made",
                "has made",
                "had made"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f8861d29da5b4d87986e4a9abe73756a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Rani has ……………….. home.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "went",
                "gone",
                "go",
                "going"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1b164f2ddd3e459bbfedf31d0021990d"
        },
        {
            "question": "We ………………. the railway station before the train arrived.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "reached",
                "have reached",
                "had reached",
                "will reach"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "633815d535eb45c9829412f0da7a7020"
        },
        {
            "question": "They do not …………………. here.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "live",
                "lived",
                "living",
                "lives"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "cd39aca4eebb4fa0bd02b7e8dfc95352"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………. editing this magazine for twenty five years by next December.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will be",
                "will have been",
                "am editing",
                "have been"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3ce62f249c62444a9c352744fad178ae"
        },
        {
            "question": "Peter …………………. two wickets before rain interrupted play.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "took",
                "had taken",
                "has taken"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "574cadf18a56401ebf6fcc3474ca2acd"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………. him twice before he left for New York.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "met",
                "had met",
                "have met"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7ff2ab064cd8486c93b12d2b3ab6f3d1"
        }
    ]
}